{
    "id": "60_Health_223",
    "claim": "The average length that can be reached goes from  to  cm; thickening can be up to  cm more than its natural circumference. The specialist is a graduate of UNAM and has a certificate from the International Academy of Penoplasty of Europe. Penoplasty is one of the most recent cosmetic operations carried out in the country to increase the length and thickness of the penis through surgery. This consists of removing from the lower abdomen the suspensory ligament of the limb to gain centimeters. This procedure has been performed in Mexico by  men by the aesthetic and reconstructive surgeon Miguelangel Guevara Montaño, certified by the International Academy of Penoplasty, in Europe, and who for three years began to offer this alternative to his patients. He has also operated abroad on  people who were looking to grow their genital limb. For any patient the average length that can be reached ranges from three to five centimeters in a state of flaccidity, depending on its physiognomy, although there are cases in which the size may be higher. On the other hand, the thickening of it can be up to four centimeters more than its natural circumference. In an interview with MILENIO at the Avant Garde clinic, Guevara who claimed to be the only certified physician performing this procedure in the country explained that'when we want to see growth in an erect state, it is more or less from  to percent\". ProcessesThe procedures for increasing length or thickness are independent and each takes around  minutes. The second consists of obtaining body fat from the abdomen or thighs, which is injected into the walls of the penis in order to increase its width.'We make a small incision of about three centimeters at the base of the pubis where we find the ligamentary structures, the penile support. We section, with very little or no bleeding, these superficial ligaments and do an extraction. If you are looking for thickening, the safest technique is to use body fat that is usually taken from the inner thigh, pubis or lower abdomen, which is prepared through a protocholyzed method and injected ', explained surgeon. There are isolated cases where the centimeters of enlargement that can be seen are greater than the average. Such is the case of one of the patientswho asked for anonymitywho went from having four centimeters of flaccid penis to  with the increase gaining a total of eight centimeters. Surgeon Guevara Montaño stressed that 'sensitivity is the same 'after surgery. Obviously there is a transition period because there is inflammation, but in the long run the sensitivity is exactly the same, 'there is no change ', and he specified that approximately *NOMBER* days after the operation patients will be able to resume their sexual life normally. Without complexesThe specialist emphasized that with this operation the complexes of many men who consider having a small penis will be able to decrease. In his testimony, a young man from  years old, who asked for anonymityinterviewed at the Avant Garde officeacknowledged that'you know when something is small and I knew that my penis was not big. That was the main reason, say, my self-esteem and security. I really measured it a few times for the same thing. I don't think I even had the motivation to do it.\". He confessed that the only person who knows about the intervention, in addition to the doctor, was his mother, who supported him and financed him to perform the procedure that has a cost of  to  thousand pesos depending on the health conditions of the patients. When you are overweight you need to perform liposuction or decrease the fat of the thighs so that you do not rub with the male limb. Regarding the cost of the operation, the UNAM graduate doctor commented that his clinic has funding so that they can pay it to monthly payments. Post-operative treatment consists of rest and the use of a hydrobomb with which they will have to perform daily exercises for  minutes, for at least eight months, to prevent the tissues from being re-retracted. If not performed, it could return to the initial size. Regarding recovery, the doctor warned that there is burning for a while and that exercise should be avoided for at least a month and a half. The scar, he concluded, is practically invisible and will be covered with hairs. I'm sorry.",
    "source": "www.milenio.com",
    "date": "14/04/2016",
    "veracity": 1,
    "claims": [
        {
            "claim": "The his length his .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did milenio.com report that his length his length?",
                    "answer": "14/04/2016"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the length of a shark?",
                    "score": 0.7485,
                    "answers": "www.milenio.com|nsubj\ton 14/04/2016|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "The specialist is a graduate of UNAM and knew a certificate from the International Academy the penis his Europe .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Where did the specialist get his certificate from?",
                    "answer": "the International Academy"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Where did the graduate of UNAM graduate from?",
                    "score": 0.814,
                    "answers": "www.milenio.com reported on 14/04/2016 that The specialist is a graduate of UNAM and knew a certificate from the International Academy the penis his Europe|ROOT\tthat The specialist is a graduate of UNAM and knew a certificate from the International Academy the penis his Europe|ccomp\tInternational|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did the graduate from UNAM do to receive his Europe certificate from the International Academy?",
                    "score": 0.7244,
                    "answers": "his Europe|appos"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of the graduate from UNAM?",
                    "score": 0.6039,
                    "answers": "www.milenio.com|nsubj\ton 14/04/2016|prep\tthat|mark\tThe|det\tThe specialist|nsubj\ta|det\ta graduate of UNAM|attr\tof UNAM|prep\tand|cc\ta|det\tthe|det\tthe|det\this|poss"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Penoplasty is one his the most measured my penis operations carried out in the country to increase the length and the ligamentary structures, the penile support his the ligamentary structures, the penile support .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What is one of the most measured my penis operations in the country?",
                    "answer": "Penoplasty"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How measured is Penoplasty?",
                    "score": 0.831,
                    "answers": "one his the most measured my penis operations carried out in the country to increase the length and the ligamentary structures , the penile support his the ligamentary structures , the penile support|attr\this the most measured my penis operations carried out in the country to increase the length and the ligamentary structures , the penile support his the ligamentary structures , the penile support|appos"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Penoplasty?",
                    "score": 0.7327,
                    "answers": "www.milenio.com|nsubj\twww.milenio.com reported on 14/04/2016 that Penoplasty is one his the most measured my penis operations carried out in the country to increase the length and the ligamentary structures , the penile support his the ligamentary structures , the penile support|ROOT\ton 14/04/2016|prep\t14/04/2016|pobj\tthat|mark\tPenoplasty|nsubj\tthat Penoplasty is one his the most measured my penis operations carried out in the country to increase the length and the ligamentary structures , the penile support his the ligamentary structures , the penile support|ccomp\this|poss\tthe|det\tmost|advmod\tmost measured|amod\tmy|poss\tpenis|compound\tcarried out in the country to increase the length and the ligamentary structures , the penile support his the ligamentary structures , the penile support|acl\tout|prt\tin the country|prep\tthe|det\tthe country|pobj\tto|aux\tto increase the length and the ligamentary structures , the penile support his the ligamentary structures , the penile support|advcl\tthe|det\tthe length and the ligamentary structures , the penile support his the ligamentary structures , the penile support|dobj\tand|cc\tthe|det\tligamentary|amod\tthe ligamentary structures , the penile support his the ligamentary structures , the penile support|conj\t,|punct\tthe|det\tpenile|amod\tthe penile support|appos\this|poss\tthe|det\tligamentary|amod\this the ligamentary structures|appos\t,|punct\tthe|det\tpenile|amod\tthe penile support|appos"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "the ligamentary structures, the penile support consists of removing the intervention abdomen the the ligamentary structures, the penile support the doctor his the ligamentary structures, the penile support limb to gain centimeters.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who is responsible for removing the intervention abdomen the ligamentary structures?",
                    "answer": "the doctor"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did the doctor do to help the ligamentary structures?",
                    "score": 0.7399,
                    "answers": "intervention|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the ligamentary structures?",
                    "score": 0.6889,
                    "answers": "on 14/04/2016|prep\t14/04/2016|pobj\tligamentary|amod\tof removing the intervention abdomen the the ligamentary structures , the penile support the doctor his the ligamentary structures ,|prep\tremoving the intervention abdomen the the ligamentary structures , the penile support the doctor his the ligamentary structures ,|pcomp\tthe intervention abdomen the the ligamentary structures , the penile support the doctor his the ligamentary structures|dobj\tligamentary|amod\tthe the ligamentary structures ,|appos\tligamentary|amod\tthe doctor his the ligamentary structures|appos\tthe penile support limb|dep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is penile support?",
                    "score": 0.6643,
                    "answers": "penile support|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the penile support?",
                    "score": 0.6608,
                    "answers": "the penile support|appos\tthe penile support|appos"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between the ligamentary and the penile support?",
                    "score": 0.6541,
                    "answers": "the penile support limb to gain centimeters|dep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Penoplasty has been performed in the country by  men by the aesthetic and reconstructive surgeon Miguelangel Guevara Montaño, certified by the International Academy of Penoplasty, in Europe , and who for three years surgeon to offer Penoplasty to patients.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Where is the International Academy of Penoplasty located?",
                    "answer": "Europe"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What type of surgery has Miguelangel Guevara Montaño performed?",
                    "score": 0.8767,
                    "answers": "reconstructive|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who certified Miguelangel Guevara Montaño for Penoplasty?",
                    "score": 0.8483,
                    "answers": "certified by the International Academy of Penoplasty , in Europe , and who for three years surgeon to offer Penoplasty to patients|acl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Penoplasty?",
                    "score": 0.8099,
                    "answers": "www.milenio.com reported on 14/04/2016 that Penoplasty has been performed in the country by   men by the aesthetic and reconstructive surgeon Miguelangel Guevara Montaño , certified by the International Academy of Penoplasty , in Europe , and who for three years surgeon to offer Penoplasty to patients|ROOT\ton 14/04/2016|prep\t14/04/2016|pobj\tthat|mark\tPenoplasty|nsubjpass\thas|aux\tbeen|auxpass\tthat Penoplasty has been performed in the country by|ccomp\tin the country|prep\tthe|det\tthe country|pobj\tby|agent\tmen|pobj\tthe|det\taesthetic and reconstructive|amod\tand|cc\tby the International Academy of Penoplasty , in Europe|agent\tthe|det\tof Penoplasty|prep\tPenoplasty|pobj\tand|cc\tto|aux\tto offer Penoplasty to patients|advcl\tPenoplasty|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the International Academy of Penoplasty?",
                    "score": 0.7972,
                    "answers": "International|compound\tthe International Academy of Penoplasty , in Europe|pobj\tin Europe|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is Miguelangel Guevara Montaño?",
                    "score": 0.7936,
                    "answers": "by the aesthetic and reconstructive surgeon Miguelangel Guevara Montaño , certified by the International Academy of Penoplasty , in Europe , and who for three years surgeon to offer Penoplasty to patients|agent\tthe aesthetic and reconstructive surgeon Miguelangel Guevara Montaño , certified by the International Academy of Penoplasty , in Europe , and who for three years surgeon to offer Penoplasty to patients|pobj\tMiguelangel|compound\tMiguelangel Guevara Montaño ,|appos"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "The specialist has also the cost of the operation the doctor people who were looking to grow their genital limb his clinic .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did milenio.com report on 14/04/2016?",
                    "answer": "the cost of the operation"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the cost of the doctor's operation?",
                    "score": 0.601,
                    "answers": "the doctor|dep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "his clinic any patient the average length the cost of the operation can be reached ranges from three to five centimeters in a state of flaccidity, depending on physiognomy, although there surgeon the size may be higher.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the average length of an operation in a state of flaccidity?",
                    "answer": "from three to five centimeters"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the average length of a surgeon's operation?",
                    "score": 0.6903,
                    "answers": "www.milenio.com|nsubj\ton 14/04/2016|prep\t14/04/2016|pobj\tany patient the average length the cost of the operation can be reached|nsubj\tthe average length the cost of the operation can be reached|appos\tthe cost of the operation can be reached|appos\tof the operation|prep\tthe operation|pobj\tcan be reached|relcl\tfrom three to five centimeters in a state of flaccidity|prep\tto five centimeters|prep\tin a state of flaccidity|prep\tdepending on physiognomy|prep\ton physiognomy|prep\tphysiognomy|pobj\talthough there surgeon the size may be higher|advcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is flaccidity?",
                    "score": 0.5951,
                    "answers": "a state of flaccidity|pobj\tof flaccidity|prep\tflaccidity|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "On the other hand, the thickening of any patient can be up to four centimeters more than natural circumference.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "How many centimeters more can thicken a patient's circumference than their natural circumference?",
                    "answer": "four centimeters"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the length of a patient's heart?",
                    "score": 0.7224,
                    "answers": "www.milenio.com|nsubj\ton 14/04/2016|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the natural circumference of a patient?",
                    "score": 0.7112,
                    "answers": "On the other hand|prep\tthe other hand|pobj\tof any patient|prep\tup to four|nummod\tup to four centimeters more than natural circumference|acomp\tthan natural circumference|prep\tnatural circumference|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "In an interview with MILENIO at the doctor Garde clinic, The specialist surgeon The specialist the operation The specialist patients that'when we want patients see growth in an erect state, surgeon  to percent\".",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.milenio.com report that in an interview with MILENIO, \"When we want patients see growth in an erect state, surgeon to percent\"?",
                    "answer": "14/04/2016"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What percentage of patients need to see growth in an erect state?",
                    "score": 0.7538,
                    "answers": "  to percent \"|dep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did Dr. MILENIO say about the specialist patients?",
                    "score": 0.663,
                    "answers": "www.milenio.com reported on 14/04/2016 that In an interview with MILENIO at the doctor Garde clinic , The specialist surgeon The specialist the operation The specialist patients that'when we want patients see growth in an erect state , surgeon   to percent \"|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many patients do the specialist surgeon The specialist the operation serve?",
                    "score": 0.6566,
                    "answers": "that In an interview with MILENIO at the doctor Garde clinic , The specialist surgeon The specialist the operation The specialist patients that'when we want patients see growth in an erect state , surgeon|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the growth rate of an erect state?",
                    "score": 0.6395,
                    "answers": "growth in an erect state|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is an erect state?",
                    "score": 0.5826,
                    "answers": "an erect state|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "ProcessesThe the operation for increasing length or thickness are independent and each takes around  minutes.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did milenio.com say about the operation for increasing length or thickness?",
                    "answer": "the operation for increasing length or thickness are independent"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How long is the process for increasing length or thickness?",
                    "score": 0.7052,
                    "answers": "on 14/04/2016|prep\teach takes|conj\taround   minutes|dep\tminutes|dobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "The second consists of obtaining body fat from the abdomen or thighs, which is injected into the walls of the penis in order to increase its width.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Where is the body fat from the abdomen or thighs injected?",
                    "answer": "injected into the walls of the penis"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How much body fat is injected into the penis to increase its width?",
                    "score": 0.7735,
                    "answers": "The second|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the purpose of injecting body fat into the walls of a penis?",
                    "score": 0.7162,
                    "answers": "on 14/04/2016|prep\tthe abdomen or thighs|pobj\tin order to increase its width|prep\torder to increase its width|pobj\tto increase its width|acl\tits width|dobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "'We make a small incision of about three centimeters at the base of the pubis where we find the ligamentary structures, the penile support.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "How many centimeters is the incision made at the base of the pubis?",
                    "answer": "three centimeters"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Where are the ligamentary structures found at the base of the pubis?",
                    "score": 0.73,
                    "answers": "www.milenio.com reported on 14/04/2016 that ' We make a small incision of about three centimeters at the base of the pubis where we find the ligamentary structures , the penile support|ROOT\tat the base of the pubis where we find the ligamentary structures , the penile support|prep\tthe base of the pubis where we find the ligamentary structures , the penile support|pobj\twhere we find the ligamentary structures , the penile support|relcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the ligamentary structures?",
                    "score": 0.7097,
                    "answers": "that|mark\t'|punct\tWe|nsubj\ta|det\tsmall|amod\tof about three centimeters|prep\tabout|advmod\tabout three|nummod\tthe|det\tthe|det\twhere|advmod\twe|nsubj\tthe|det\tligamentary|amod\t,|punct\tthe|det\tpenile|amod\tthe penile support|appos"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the ligamentary structure of a pubis?",
                    "score": 0.7066,
                    "answers": "of the pubis|prep\tthe pubis|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "We section, with very little or no bleeding, these superficial ligaments and do an extraction.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did milenio.com report that we sectioned the superficial ligaments with very little bleeding?",
                    "answer": "14/04/2016"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What are the superficial ligaments?",
                    "score": 0.7087,
                    "answers": "these superficial ligaments|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the process used to remove the superficial ligaments?",
                    "score": 0.7014,
                    "answers": "www.milenio.com reported on 14/04/2016 that We section , with very little or no bleeding , these superficial ligaments and do an extraction|ROOT\tthat|mark\tWe|nsubj\tthat We section , with very little or no bleeding , these superficial ligaments and do an extraction|ccomp\t,|punct\tor|cc\t,|punct\tthese|det\tand|cc\tdo an extraction|conj\tan|det\tan extraction|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the amount of bleeding from the superficial ligaments?",
                    "score": 0.675,
                    "answers": "with very little or no bleeding|prep\tvery little or no bleeding|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Milenio.com?",
                    "score": 0.518,
                    "answers": "www.milenio.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "If you are looking for thickening, the safest technique is to use body fat that is usually taken from the inner thigh, pubis or lower abdomen, which is prepared through a protocholyzed method and injected ', explained surgeon.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What happens to body fat that is taken from the inner thigh, pubis or lower abdomen?",
                    "answer": "injected"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How much body fat is taken from inner thigh, pubis, or lower abdomen for thickening?",
                    "score": 0.7382,
                    "answers": "surgeon|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the safest method to use for thickening?",
                    "score": 0.6632,
                    "answers": "on 14/04/2016|prep\tIf|mark\tyou|nsubj\tIf you are looking for thickening|advcl\tfor thickening|prep\tthickening|pobj\tsafest|amod\tthe safest technique|nsubj\tthat If you are looking for thickening , the safest technique is to use body fat that is usually taken from the inner thigh , pubis or lower abdomen which is prepared through a protocholyzed method and injected ,|ccomp\tto|aux\tthe inner thigh , pubis or lower abdomen which is prepared through a protocholyzed method and injected|pobj\tor|cc\twhich is prepared through a protocholyzed method and injected|relcl\tand|cc"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the best method to measure body fat?",
                    "score": 0.635,
                    "answers": "a protocholyzed method|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What method is used to develop this method?",
                    "score": 0.6046,
                    "answers": "protocholyzed|amod"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "There are isolated cases where the centimeters of enlargement that can be seen are greater than the average.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "How are the centimeters of enlargement seen in isolated cases?",
                    "answer": "greater than the average"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many cases of enlargement can be seen?",
                    "score": 0.7914,
                    "answers": "www.milenio.com reported on 14/04/2016 that There are isolated cases where the centimeters of enlargement that can be seen are greater than the average|ROOT\tThere|expl\tisolated|amod\tisolated cases where the centimeters of enlargement that can be seen are greater than the average|attr"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the average size of an isolated case of enlargement?",
                    "score": 0.7369,
                    "answers": "that There are isolated cases where the centimeters of enlargement that can be seen are greater than the average|ccomp\tthe average|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the averageimeter of enlargement that can be seen?",
                    "score": 0.6902,
                    "answers": "www.milenio.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Such is the case of one of the patientswho asked for anonymitywho went from having four centimeters of flaccid penis to  with the increase gaining a total of eight centimeters.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "How many centimeters of flaccid penis did the patient have?",
                    "answer": "four centimeters"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many centimeters of flaccid penis did the patients have?",
                    "score": 0.7115,
                    "answers": "a|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many centimeters did the patients who asked for anonymity have?",
                    "score": 0.6801,
                    "answers": "  with the increase gaining a total of eight centimeters|dep\tthe increase gaining a total of eight centimeters|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is flaccid penis?",
                    "score": 0.659,
                    "answers": "flaccid|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the difference between a penis and a penis?",
                    "score": 0.6389,
                    "answers": "with the increase gaining a total of eight centimeters|prep\tgaining a total of eight centimeters|acl"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Surgeon Guevara Montaño stressed that 'sensitivity is the same 'after surgery.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Surgeon Guevara Montao say?",
                    "answer": "'sensitivity is the same 'after surgery"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Guevara Montaño say about surgery?",
                    "score": 0.8008,
                    "answers": "www.milenio.com reported on 14/04/2016 that Surgeon Guevara Montaño stressed that ' sensitivity is the same ' after surgery|ROOT\ton 14/04/2016|prep\tthat|mark\tthat|mark\t'|punct\t'|punct"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Guevara Montaño's opinion on surgery?",
                    "score": 0.7691,
                    "answers": "Surgeon Guevara Montaño|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between tolerance and sensitivity after surgery?",
                    "score": 0.6685,
                    "answers": "that Surgeon Guevara Montaño stressed that ' sensitivity is the same ' after surgery|ccomp\tsensitivity|nsubj\tthat ' sensitivity is the same ' after surgery|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the difference between surgery and surgery after surgery?",
                    "score": 0.6523,
                    "answers": "the same|attr"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Obviously there is a transition period because there is inflammation, but in the long run the sensitivity is exactly the same, 'there is no change ', and he specified that approximately *NOMBER* days after the operation patients will be able to resume their sexual life normally.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did www.milenio.com say about the sensitivity in the long run?",
                    "answer": "no change"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many days after an operation will patients be able to resume their sexual life normally?",
                    "score": 0.6816,
                    "answers": "their sexual life|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the transition period for an individual to regain their sexual life?",
                    "score": 0.6557,
                    "answers": "www.milenio.com reported on 14/04/2016 that Obviously there is a transition period because there is inflammation , but in the long run the sensitivity is exactly the same , ' there is no change ' , and he specified that approximately * NOMBER * days after the operation patients will be able to resume their sexual life normally|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the time difference between a doctor's surgery and a patient's sexual life after surgery?",
                    "score": 0.607,
                    "answers": "NOMBER * days after the operation|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between inflammation and sexual life in the long run?",
                    "score": 0.5917,
                    "answers": "in the long run|prep\tin the long run the sensitivity is exactly the same , ' there is no change|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the difference between an operation and an operation?",
                    "score": 0.5875,
                    "answers": "exactly the same|attr"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Without complexesThe specialist emphasized that with this operation the complexes of many men who consider having a small penis will be able to decrease.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did the specialist say would be able to decrease with the operation without complexes?",
                    "answer": "the complexes of many men who consider having a small penis"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many men consider having a small penis?",
                    "score": 0.751,
                    "answers": "of many men who consider having a small penis|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How much will the complexes of men who consider having small penis be able to decrease?",
                    "score": 0.7265,
                    "answers": "that with this operation the complexes of many men who consider having a small penis will be able to decrease|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between a large penis and a small penis?",
                    "score": 0.6723,
                    "answers": "on 14/04/2016|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the impact of having a small penis on a man's life?",
                    "score": 0.6716,
                    "answers": "will|aux"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the difference between a small penis and a large penis?",
                    "score": 0.6682,
                    "answers": "with this operation|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "In his testimony, a young man from  years old, who asked for anonymityinterviewed at the Avant Garde officeacknowledged that'you know when something is small and I knew that my penis was not big.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did a young man who asked for anonymity say in his testimony?",
                    "answer": "that'you know when something is small and I knew that my penis was not big"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did a young man say about his penis?",
                    "score": 0.6167,
                    "answers": "that In his testimony , a young man from   years old , who asked for anonymityinterviewed at the Avant Garde officeacknowledged that'you know something is small and when I knew that my penis was not big|ccomp\tthat'you know something is small and when I knew that my penis was not big|ccomp\twhen I knew that my penis was not big|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How old was the man who asked for anonymityinterviewed at the Avant Garde office?",
                    "score": 0.5063,
                    "answers": "  years old|appos\told|amod"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "That was the main reason, say, my self-esteem and security.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.milenio.com report that it was the main reason for my self-esteem and security?",
                    "answer": "14/04/2016"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the main reason for a person's self-esteem and security?",
                    "score": 0.7139,
                    "answers": "www.milenio.com reported on 14/04/2016 that That was the main reason , say , my self - esteem and security|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the reason for self-esteem and security?",
                    "score": 0.7037,
                    "answers": "on 14/04/2016|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the relationship between self-esteem and security?",
                    "score": 0.653,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tThat|nsubj\tthe|det\t,|punct\tsay|intj\t,|punct\tmy|poss\tmy self -|appos\t-|conj\testeem and security|appos\tand|cc\tsecurity|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Milenio.com?",
                    "score": 0.5597,
                    "answers": "www.milenio.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "I really measured it a few times for the same thing.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "How many times did I measure it for the same thing?",
                    "answer": "measured it a few times"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the method used to measure inflation?",
                    "score": 0.8554,
                    "answers": "on 14/04/2016|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many times has it measured the same thing a few times?",
                    "score": 0.8528,
                    "answers": "the same thing|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What ismilenio.com?",
                    "score": 0.6218,
                    "answers": "www.milenio.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "I don't think I even had the motivation to do it.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did milenio.com report that I didn't think I had the motivation to do it?",
                    "answer": "14/04/2016"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the motivation to do it?",
                    "score": 0.8258,
                    "answers": "that I do n't think I even had the motivation to do it|ccomp\tI even had the motivation to do it|ccomp\tthe motivation to do it|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What ismilenio.com?",
                    "score": 0.7053,
                    "answers": "www.milenio.com|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Milenio.com?",
                    "score": 0.7017,
                    "answers": "www.milenio.com reported on 14/04/2016 that I do n't think I even had the motivation to do it|ROOT\ton 14/04/2016|prep\tthat|mark\tI|nsubj\tdo|aux\tI|nsubj\teven|advmod\tthe|det\tto|aux\tit|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of Milenio.com?",
                    "score": 0.6241,
                    "answers": "n't|neg"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "He confessed that the only person who knows about the intervention, in addition to the doctor, was his mother, who supported him and financed him to perform the procedure that has a cost of  to  thousand pesos depending on the health conditions of the patients.",
            "question_answers": [],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many people know about the intervention of Dr. Rodrigo Duterte?",
                    "score": 0.6433,
                    "answers": "He|nsubj\tonly|amod\twho|nsubj\taddition to the doctor|pobj\this|poss\twho|nsubj\thim|dobj\thim|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the cost of the procedure that Dr. Milenio performed?",
                    "score": 0.5958,
                    "answers": "www.milenio.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "When you are overweight you need to perform liposuction or decrease the fat of the thighs so that you do not rub with the male limb.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did milenio.com report on 14/04/2016",
                    "answer": "When you are overweight you need to perform liposuction or decrease the fat of the thighs"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How do you decrease the fat of the thighs when you are overweight?",
                    "score": 0.8404,
                    "answers": "with the male limb|prep\tthe male limb|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does it mean to be overweight?",
                    "score": 0.7626,
                    "answers": "When you are overweight|advcl\toverweight|acomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the symptoms of being overweight?",
                    "score": 0.7255,
                    "answers": "that When you are overweight you need to perform liposuction or decrease the fat of the thighs so that you do not rub with the male limb|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the benefits of liposuction for overweight people?",
                    "score": 0.7192,
                    "answers": "www.milenio.com|nsubj\tso that you do not rub with the male limb|advcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the process used to perform liposuction?",
                    "score": 0.6898,
                    "answers": "the thighs|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Regarding the cost of the operation, the UNAM graduate doctor commented that his clinic has funding so that they can pay it to monthly payments.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did the UNAM graduate doctor say about the cost of the operation?",
                    "answer": "his clinic has funding so that they can pay it to monthly payments"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How much money did the UNAM graduate doctor receive for his clinic operation in 2016?",
                    "score": 0.7221,
                    "answers": "that his clinic has funding so that they can pay it to monthly payments|ccomp\tto monthly payments|prep\tmonthly payments|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the cost of the UNAM graduate doctor's clinic operation?",
                    "score": 0.7192,
                    "answers": "www.milenio.com|nsubj\tthat|mark\tthe|det\tthe|det\t,|punct\tthe|det\tthat|mark\this|poss\tso|mark\tthat|mark\tthey|nsubj\tcan|aux\tso that they can pay it to monthly payments|advcl\tit|dobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Post-operative treatment consists of rest and the use of a hydrobomb with which they will have to perform daily exercises for  minutes, for at least eight months, to prevent the tissues from being re-retracted.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the purpose of using a hydrobomb?",
                    "answer": "to prevent the tissues from being re-retracted"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How long do post-operative treatment consist of rest and use of hydrobomb?",
                    "score": 0.725,
                    "answers": "at least eight|nummod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the purpose of Post-operative treatment?",
                    "score": 0.6359,
                    "answers": "on 14/04/2016|prep\tPost|amod\tPost - operative treatment|nsubj\tthat Post - operative treatment consists of rest and the use of a hydrobomb with which they will have to perform daily exercises for|ccomp\twith which they will have to perform daily exercises for|relcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Milenio.com?",
                    "score": 0.4782,
                    "answers": "www.milenio.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "If not performed, it could return to the initial size.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did milenio.com report that if not performed, it could return to the initial size?",
                    "answer": "14/04/2016"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the initial size of a new instrument?",
                    "score": 0.8295,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tIf|mark\tnot|neg\t,|punct\tit|nsubj\tcould|aux\tthe|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What ismilenio.com?",
                    "score": 0.6025,
                    "answers": "www.milenio.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Regarding recovery, the doctor warned that there is burning for a while and that exercise should be avoided for at least a month and a half.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "How long should exercise be avoided?",
                    "answer": "at least a month and a half"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did the doctor warned about burning for a while?",
                    "score": 0.6904,
                    "answers": "Regarding recovery|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the process of recovery?",
                    "score": 0.622,
                    "answers": "recovery|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the symptoms of burning for at least a month and a half?",
                    "score": 0.6109,
                    "answers": "that Regarding recovery , the doctor warned that there is burning for a while and that exercise should be avoided for at least a month and a half|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between burning and recovery according to the doctor?",
                    "score": 0.592,
                    "answers": "for a while|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "The scar, he concluded, is practically invisible and will be covered with hairs.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "How does the scar look to the naked eye?",
                    "answer": "invisible"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How will the scar be covered with hairs?",
                    "score": 0.8488,
                    "answers": "will|aux"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the hairs on a scar?",
                    "score": 0.7502,
                    "answers": ",|punct\t,|punct\tbe|auxpass"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the difference between a scar and a scar?",
                    "score": 0.6897,
                    "answers": "on 14/04/2016|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the purpose of the scar?",
                    "score": 0.6838,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tThe|det\tThe scar|nsubj\the|nsubj\tpractically|advmod\tpractically invisible|acomp\tand|cc"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the size of the scar?",
                    "score": 0.6525,
                    "answers": "www.milenio.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}